

Khaled AL-Sheikh Oghli

WEB DESIGNER & UI

CONTACT

NAME khalid Al shikh oghli

PHONE +963 956798809

EMAIL khalidoghli7@gmail.com

Facebook facebook.com/khalidOghli

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/khalidoghli

CodePen codepen.io/khalidOghli

HOBBIES









WEB DESIGN

GRAPHIC DESIGN

UI DESIGN

FRONT-END

BACK-END



PROFILE

I've got 2+ years of experience in WEB-DESIGN like: designing and maintenance many website and user interface ,Also during those years i've got some of practical experience of ux and seo and programming.

All of that paved my way to be a med Web Designer. Based on that i'm really passionate about all kind of design, every single day i'm reading new articles, studying, practice and looking for getting a high designing skills.



EDUCATION

AL-andalous High Shcool Bachelor

2015- 2013

2020 - 2016



Technical Computer Collage

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Time Mangement

Leadership

Teamwork

Creativity



EXPERIENCE



2018- 2017

Targus Me

I spent two months training in this company and then worked there for about 4 months as web designer until I returned to collage

2019- 2018

Cyber Tech

worked there for about 5 months as web designer in the summer vacation until i returned to collage too.

veen these two years i worked on individual projects to train at home and studied a lot...

CERTIFICATES

Coursera Certificates

Introduction to javascript University of Michigan

February/ 2019

January/ 2019

January/ 2019

August/2018

How to Write a Resume

February/ 2019 The State University of New York

Advanced Styling Responsive Design

University of Michigan January/ 2019

Introduction to CSS3 University of Michigan

Learning How To Learn for Youth

Arizona State University **Udemy Certificates**

Code Your First Game: Arcade Classic in JavaScript on Canvas Udemy

December/2018

Microsoft Certificates

HTML5 & CSS3 Fundamentals: Development

Microsoft Visual Academy **Edraak Certificates**

UX Design Edraak

August/2018

See Certificates in LinkedIn.com/in/khalidoghli



LANGUAGES





TECH SKILLS

HTML/HTML5

CSS/CSS3

JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY

BOOTSTRAP

RESPONSIVE ANIMATION

PS

ΑI

VUE JS SEO

UX

Learning...

Learning...

Learning...